<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our Project on Synergos</title><link>/project/</link><description>Recent content in Our Project on Synergos</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2021 SYNERGOS. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI Chatbot</title><link>/project/rio-furniture-5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/rio-furniture-5/</guid><description>Build an AI Interactive Chatbot Dialogflow is a authoring tool that enables EFL teachers to customize a chatbot from scratch. Teachers can devise a general-purpose bot, a speaking-test bot, a listening-test bot, a purpose-built bot, a quiz bot, etc.</description></item><item><title>LINE &amp; Pandorabot</title><link>/project/rio-furniture-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/rio-furniture-1/</guid><description>General-Purpose Chatbot Design The project aims to leverage the open-source AIML files to build a chatbot on LINE. EFL teachers can customize the chatbot&amp;rsquo;s properties. They can also add some phrases they would like to teach to the chatbot&amp;rsquo;s knowledge bank.</description></item><item><title>News Web Crawler</title><link>/project/rio-furniture-9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/rio-furniture-9/</guid><description>News Article Crawler Teacher Request
It is time consuming to collect articles one by one. Especially when teachers are searching for articles with specific sentence patterns, it is tiring to look for information.</description></item><item><title>Oxford Dictionary API</title><link>/project/rio-furniture-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/rio-furniture-2/</guid><description>Automatic Data Retrieval from Oxford Dictionary With Python, EFL teachers can make the most use of definitions, examples, phonetic spelling and other entries provided by Oxford Dictionary. They can write a script to automate tasks, which will save much time, especially when it is combined with authoring tools such as Quizlet.</description></item><item><title>Random Name Picker</title><link>/project/rio-furniture-8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/rio-furniture-8/</guid><description>Randomly pick a name Teacher Request
In classroom, sometimes we use Wheel of Names as the name picker. I want to design other kinds of name pickers. It may make class activities more interesting.</description></item><item><title>Speech to Text</title><link>/project/rio-furniture-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/rio-furniture-4/</guid><description>Google Speech-to-Text Service An EFL teacher was doing research. She collected some interview recordings. Manually transcribing these audio files is really a waste of time. With Python, we wrote a program automatically converting audio files into texts, which saved lots of time.</description></item><item><title>Teacher Community</title><link>/project/rio-furniture-6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/rio-furniture-6/</guid><description>CALL Community to Brainstorm In 2021, we started to hold workshops for EFL teachers. Then I created a platform to exchange ideas. We are looking forward to innovative applications. I am also looking for better ways for these EFL teachers to benefit from Python and other tech tools.</description></item><item><title>Test Shuffle</title><link>/project/rio-furniture-7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/rio-furniture-7/</guid><description>Suffle Test Questions Teacher Request
Because the students in my school are not good enough and the students are more passive in learning, I became a teacher who gave out small exam papers to students in every class, and because I had to teach different grades at the same time, the amount of lesson preparation every day was huge.</description></item><item><title>Text-to-Speech</title><link>/project/rio-furniture-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/rio-furniture-3/</guid><description>Converting texts to audio files through Python Azure provides service to convert texts to speech. They claim that they use AI technology, which enables the voice to be as natural as possible.</description></item></channel></rss>